（♪♪）
♪♪
[Hobbs]
你在这里是因为
You are here because
你弟弟明天会和我们一起
your brother
will join us tomorrow.
我知道你和我前任有过约定
I know that you and my
predecessor had an arrangement,
但我不叫卡里姆
but I am not Kareem.
这是我的城堡
This is my castle now.
凯尔打了我
我他妈成了恶人
Kyle shot me,
and I'm the fucking bad guy.
告诉他们你为什么这么做
Tell them why you did it.
特蕾丝 这是纸牌屋
This is a house
of fucking cards, Trace,
我可不能让它倒了
and I can't be the reason
that it comes falling down.
把索耶交出来
Give me Sawyer.
我会忘了查理和莫里西
I'll forget about
Charlie and Morrissey.
- 我帮不了你
- 真可惜
- I can't help you.
- That's a shame.
♪ 戏剧性音乐 ♪
♪ dramatic music ♪
[火车汽笛声]
[train horn blows]
[伊恩] 这该死的火车
[Ian]
This fucking train
这个……这是我们未知的魔鬼
- decapitated these fuckers.
- [Mike] Jesus.
[Raphael]
__SUBX_FMT_1__波哥大不会让步__SUBX_FMT_2__
Well, this... this is
the devil we don't know.
看来我们得坚持上次那笔
[Raphael]
Bogotá's not budging.
- 扯淡
- 不照办 我们就争吵
Looks like we gonna have to
stand by that last installment.
迈克 有人朝大佬开枪
- Bullshit.
- We don't, we squabble.
[警笛声]
Mike. Somebody took a shot
at the big man.
如果我兄弟出事
[sirens wailing]
__SUBX_FMT_1__会有后果__SUBX_FMT_2__
If anything happens
to my brother,
[Callahan]
想活命就别去医务室
就在这儿养伤
there's gonna be consequences.
[呻吟声]
[grunts, groans]
♪ 沉思音乐 ♪
[Callahan]
You want to live,
我信奉耶稣基督 祂的独生子 我们的主
do not go to sick bay.
由圣灵感孕
You heal right here.
被钉十字架 受死 埋葬
♪ pensive music ♪
降在阴间…… [继续含糊不清]
I believe in Jesus Christ,
His only son, our Lord,
[Barnes]
就是今天 就是今天
conceived by the Holy Ghost,
不是他妈明天
was crucified,
died and was buried.
不 不 必须今天
He descended into Hell...
[continues indistinctly]
他们撒谎!
他们总撒谎!
[Barnes]
Today is the day, today,
[祈祷的囚犯]
……永生 阿门
not fucking tomorrow.
我们在天上的父
愿人都尊你的名为圣
No, no. It'll have to be.
他们他妈的在撒谎！总是在撒谎！
They fucking lie!
They always lie!
[祈祷的囚犯]
...以及永生 阿门
[praying inmate]
...and life everlasting. Amen.
我们在天上的父
愿人都尊你的名为圣
Our Father, who art in Heaven,
hallowed be Thy Name.
愿你的国降临
愿你的旨意成就
Thy kingdom come,
Thy will be done,
- 在地上如同在天上
♪ 缓慢 庄严的音乐 ♪
- on Earth as it is in heaven.
- ♪ slow, solemn music ♪
今日赐我
日用饮食
Give us this day
our daily bread.
- [呻吟声]
- [祷告的囚犯] 宽恕那些
- [groans]
- [praying inmate] Forgive those
- 得罪我们的人...
[哼声]
- who trespass against us...
- [grunts]
[模糊说话声]
[indistinct chatter]
[祈祷的囚犯] 救我们脱离邪恶...
[praying inmate]
Deliver us from evil...
[凯尔轻声呻吟]
[Kyle groaning softly]
安顿下来真不容易
Settling in is a bitch.
[凯尔呻吟]
就没消停过
- [Kyle groans]
- Never easy.
[模糊的祈祷声]
[indistinct praying]
兄弟你还活着？
You alive, brother?
敲一下表示同意
敲两下表示拒绝
Knock once for "yes,"
twice for "no."
[巴恩斯]
都过了一个礼拜了 见鬼
[Barnes]
Been over a week, goddamn it.
今天我见到辅导员了！
I got to see my counselor today!
今天 就他妈今天
T-O-D-A-Y, to-fucking-day!
[咕哝声]
快放我出笼子！
[grunts]
Get me out of this cage!
我需要见我的辅导员！
I need to see my counselor!
我一周没见到辅导员了 好吗 该死！
I haven't seen my counselor
in a week, okay?! Goddamn it!
[低吼声]
[grunts]
♪ 缓慢悬疑音乐
该死
- ♪ slow, suspenseful music
- Shit.
[囚犯祈祷]
愿人都尊你的名为圣
[praying inmate]
...hallowed be Thy name.
巴恩斯，离栏杆远点！
Barnes, step away from the bars!
你明天去见心理咨询师，好吗
You're seeing your counselor
tomorrow, okay?
少废话 安静点
[巴恩斯] 过来
- Cut the bullshit. Be quiet.
- [Barnes] Get over here!
我不认识你
Hey, I don't know you.
天哪 听我说
Oh, God. Listen to me.
- 我...
- 他们昨晚告诉你了
- I...
- They told you last night
你明天去见心理咨询师 我保证
that you're seeing your
counselor tomorrow, I promise.
离开栏杆
Step away from the bars.
[Cindy] 退后...
[Cindy]
Step away...
- 你个混蛋
- 从栏杆那…走开…
- You cunt.
- from the bars. Step... away...
- 混蛋！
- 快！
- You cunt!
- Now!
我信圣灵
我信圣徒相通
I believe in the Holy Spirit,
the communion of saints
罪得赦免  身体复活
the forgiveness of sins,
the resurrection
身体的复活与永生
of the body
and life everlasting.
- [咕哝声]
- 天哪！
- [grunts]
- Oh, my God!
[呻吟声]
[groaning]
[Kyle]
警官?
Officer?
警官 呼叫支援
Officer, call for backup.
- [喘息]
- Stephens 我需要帮助
- [panting]
- Stephens, I need help
在行政隔离牢房 我需要立即支援
有一名犯人倒下了
in Ad Seg. I need immediate
backup. We got a prisoner down.
一名囚犯倒下了
需要立即支援
We got a prisoner down.
I need immediate backup.
[囚犯喧闹声]
[inmates clamoring]
[锁鸣响]
[lock buzzes]
[辛迪] 快打911！
[Cindy]
Call 911!
[Cindy呻吟声]
[Cindy groans]
[Clyde]
我操
Holy fuck.
[布林] 叫船长下来
[Breen]
Get the captain down here.
- [囚犯们吵闹声]
- [呼气]
- [inmates clamoring]
- [exhales]
该死的周一
Fucking Mondays.
[辛迪呻吟声]
[Cindy groaning]
♪ 缓慢而引人入胜的音乐 ♪
♪ slow, intriguing music ♪
（♪）
♪
[引擎轰鸣声]
[engine revving]
我正往你那里赶 上车了
I'm on my way to you. Getting in
在霍布斯到达之前
好吗
before Hobbs gets there,
all right?
确保
门口没有乱七八糟的事
Make sure
there's no bullshit at the gate.
[轮胎尖叫声]
[tires squealing]
好的 我马上处理
卡尼 你要是真的在处理
- All right. I'm on it.
- Carney, if you were on it,
这一切就不会发生了 对吗
none of this would be happening,
would it?
如果你在上面 我弟弟就不会
If you were on it,
my brother wouldn't be
一个该死的沙袋
如果你在上面...
a fucking punching bag.
If you were on it...
[吸气声]
[inhales]
我他妈在尽全力 我向你保证
I'm doing what the fuck I can,
I promise you,
- 我试试。
- 你现在在吃饭吗？
- I'll try.
- Are you eating right now?
我他妈在吃早饭
Yeah, I'm fucking eating.
It's breakfast.
老天爷 卡尼
这不是吃零食的时候
Jesus Christ, Carney.
This is not snack time.
我会帮你通过大门
好吗？
I'll get you through the gate,
all right?
我会盯住Kyle
这是我尽力而为了
And I'll keep my eyes on Kyle,
that's... the best I can do.
这位新监狱长和她的小副手托雷斯——
This new warden
and her little deputy, Torres--
靠 他们夹住我蛋了
shit, they've-they've got
my balls in a vice.
我没啥话语权
I've got no sway.
卡尼 是时候露出个笑脸了
Carney, I think it's time
maybe you put on a smile,
握握手
交个新朋友
shake some hands,
make some new friends,
给我想办法搞定
figure it the fuck out.
[引擎轰鸣声]
[engine revving]
隔离区那个管教是谁？
新的那个？
What's that CO in Ad Seg?
The new one?
- 你喜欢的那个人？
- 辛迪...斯蒂芬斯。怎么了？
- The one you have a crush on?
- Cindy... Stephens. Why?
Russell 家今晚
下班后到那儿
Russell's tonight.
After you clock out, be there.
我想见她
谢谢 再见
I want to meet her.
Thank you. Bye.
- [电话铃声]
- [叹气]
- [line ringing]
- [sighs]
- 嗨 我是特蕾西 请...
- 操 该死的
- Hi. This is Tracy. Please...
- Fuck. Goddamn it.
...留个言
我会回复你
...leave a message.
and I'll get back to you
- 尽快
- [哔声]
- as soon as possible.
- [beep]
嘿 Trace 是我
Hey, Trace, it's me.
听着 在你去见凯尔之前
Look, before you go visit Kyle,
请先给我打电话
这很重要
please call me first.
It's important.
-谢谢你
- Thank you.
- [火车信号铃声]
- 操！
- [train signal bell clanging]
- Fuck!
[轮胎尖叫声]
[tires squealing]
- [火车鸣笛声]
- [铃铛敲击声]
- [train horn blowing]
- [bell clanging]
[引擎轰鸣声]
[轮胎尖叫声]
- [engine revving]
- [tires squealing]
[伊恩] 我们再试一次
[Ian]
Let's try this again.
你他妈的叫什么名字
- 你叫什么名字
- What's your fucking name?
- ¿Cómo se llama?
律师
Abogado.
Who told you
to take out Bunny Washington?
- 律师
- [Ian] 好吧 不管了
- Abogado.
- [Ian] Okay, fuck it.
我要说个大词
混蛋 "互惠"
I'm gonna throw a big word down
here, fucker. "Reciprocity."
知道那是什么意思吗
就是你要给我点东西
Know what that means?
Means you give me something,
我还你些东西
告诉我谁下的令
I give you something back. Now,
you tell me who called the hit,
我给你找个律师
你他妈给我滚出去
I get you a fucking lawyer,
you walk the fuck out of here.
律师
Abogado.
该死 说英语 请
Fucking Jesus Christ,
English, por favor.
- 律师
- Abogado.
- "Abo..."
没人关心你的牛油果 好吗？
Nobody cares
about your avocados. All right?
没人他妈的在乎
Nobody gives a fuck.
我明白你的意思
"我需要一名律师"
I get what you're saying.
"I need a lawyer."
你没身份证 混蛋
你根本不存在
You got no ID, fucker.
You don't fucking exist.
我是这么想的 不如让你
So, here's what I'm thinking.
Maybe we put you
楼下那该死的牢房 嗯？
downstairs in a goddamn cell.
Huh?
你明白吗，朋友？
¿Comprende, amigo?
帮你自己个忙 给我点东西
And do yourself a fucking favor.
Give me something
用我的母语 我知道你他妈会说
in my native tongue.
I know you fucking speak it.
Hablo 英语
快点 巴勃罗
Hablo English.
Come on, Pablo.
我说英语 我说
Hablo English. Hablo.
[嘲笑] Hablo 英语?
[mocking]
Hablo English?
[尖声]
我说英语？
[high-pitched]
Hablo English?
♪ 缓慢紧张的音乐
去你妈的
- ♪ slow, suspenseful music
- Fuck you.
我跟你说过！你欠我
五块钱 谢谢先生
I told you! You owe me
five bucks. Thank you, sir.
- 操！
- 谢谢老大
- Motherfucker.
- Thanks, big boss.
♪ 紧张而充满氛围的音乐 ♪
♪ tense, atmospheric music ♪
♪ 她将驾着六匹白马 ♪
♪ She'll be driving
six white horses ♪
♪ 赶着六匹
白马 ♪
♪ Driving six
white horses ♪
♪ 驾着六匹白马
当她到来 ♪
♪ Driving six white horses
when she comes ♪
[车门关闭声]
[vehicle door closes]
听说你昨天有点麻烦
Heard you had
some static yesterday.
分心
Distractions.
波哥大 去追俄罗斯人 冲我来
Bogotá go after the Russians,
come at me,
我很快会去拜访他们
I'll pay 'em a visit soon.
- 是吗？
- 嗯
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
不是哥伦比亚人毁了布莱顿海滩
It wasn't the Colombians
took out Brighton Beach.
是你吗？
That you?
送我进取的弟弟的礼物
A gift to my enterprising
young brother.
让你看看我的意图
Show you my intent.
你想要什么回报？
What you expect in return?
合伙吧 我一直在观察你 德维林
Partnership, 'cause
I've been watching you, Deverin.
赢得这一切 来之不易
What you won's been hard-fought.
- 你需要一个盟友
- 我以前从不需要
- You need an ally.
- I never did before.
你的莫斯科行动给我们腾出了些好地盘
Well, your move on Moscow opened
up some prime real estate.
俄罗斯人守住了那条边境管道
The Russians held
that border pipeline
多年来 现在成了真空
for years,
and now there's a vacuum.
他们会回来填补空缺
或者墨西哥人 雅利安人
And they'll come back and fill
it, or the Mexicans, the Aryans.
卡特尔刚想
把你干掉
I mean, the cartel just tried
to take you out.
现在 我懂了
Now, I'd see
你可以保留你赚到的 Deverin
that you get to keep
what you've earned, Deverin.
只有家人才这么叫我 弗兰克
Only family call me that, Frank.
靠
Well, shit.
[两人笑]
[both laughs]
兔子就是用来追的 对吧
A rabbit's something
to be chased, right?
一个可怕的生物
A fearful creature.
是你吗 儿子？
你害怕吗？
Now, is that you, son?
Are you fearful?
天不怕地不怕
Don't fear a goddamn thing.
现在我很感谢这份礼物
Now, I'm thankful for the gift.
你想要什么回报
What do you want in return?
未来
A future.
你上来吗
You coming up or not?
好吧
All right.
嗨 杰克
我们私下处理
Yo, Jake,
we're doing this private.
["Time Out" 由Count Basie和他的管弦乐队演奏]
["Time Out" by Count Basie
and His Orchestra playing]
（♪）
♪
我是个绝缘体 D
I'm an insulated man, D,
被合法化的人
a legitimized man.
我外包 特许经营 授权
I outsource, I franchise,
I delegate.
我们现在坐的这块地盘
归我所有
I own this yard
we're sitting in right now,
我用它来运货
and I use it to run product.
我提供的是跨境运输
And what I offer you is
cross-border transport.
安保 抽成30%
Security. For 30%.
（♪）
♪
十个更好
Ten sound better.
那就20
折中
20, then. Split the difference.
好 我们动手吧
All right. We gonna do this.
但恕我直言 我了解你的名声
But with respect,
I know your rep,
我可不相信任何人的鬼话
but I ain't in the business of
taking anybody's word for shit.
我听到了
I hear you.
我会见所有头目
I'm gonna meet every player,
驿马快递的
每个骑手
every rider
on this here Pony Express.
我别无他求
I wouldn't have it
any other way.
你要见个人
You're gonna meet
网络里的每个人
everybody in the network.
我这人有仇必报 D
See, I'm in the business
of paying shit forward, D.
真的
For real.
不过我也有个请求
But I have a request, too.
你刚才说错了
You misspoke before.
你有个搭档
You have a partner.
是时候见见市长了
It's time I met the mayor.
[轻笑]
[chuckling]
- 迈克
- 霍布斯
- Mike.
- Hobbs.
早知道你在这 我就
Had I known you'd be here,
I would've
点了两份
ordered for two
at the drive-thru.
你想告诉我？
So, you want to tell me
他妈的发生什么事了
what the fuck happened?
我们刚谈过这事
I mean,
we just talked about this.
但不到24小时后
But not 24 hours later,
我弟弟在你的监狱里被打得遍体鳞伤
my brother gets beaten
to a pulp in your prison.
想解释一下吗
Want to explain that?
- 你哥哥——
- 凯尔
- Your brother--
- Kyle.
麦克拉斯基？
对
好
- McLusky. Yeah.
- Right.
很抱歉 Kyle 打架了
I am sorry
that Kyle got into a fight.
打架？这里不是操场
Fight?
It's not a playground.
- 不 不是的
- 对吧 对吧？
- No. No, it is not.
- Right? Right?
但你知道这世界 迈克 你了解这行当
But you know the world, Mike,
you know this life.
嗯哼
我控制不了
- Mm-hmm.
- I am not in control
每个变量的所有情况
联系别人不是我的工作
of every variable, and it is not
my job to reach out
每次出事都要联系家里
to family every time
there's an incident.
可你昨天不是这么唱的
Not what you sang yesterday.
你铁腕统治
You rule with an iron fist.
可表面却那么温柔
But a velvet glove.
迈克 我还在安顿
给我点时间
I am still settling in, Mike.
Just give me a beat.
对
Yeah.
既然你无法履行你的承诺
Well, if you can't hold up
your end of the bargain,
我撑不住了
I can't hold up mine.
我们没有交易
We have no bargain.
哦 所以你没答应照顾我弟弟？
Oh, so you didn't promise
to look after my brother?
我说过
会留他一命 他活着吗？
I told you
I would keep him alive. Is he?
我一向说到做到
I am a woman of my word.
♪ 缓慢阴沉的声音 ♪
♪ slow, ominous music ♪
好 从现在开始...
Okay, from this point on...
[叹气声]
[sighs]
...我兄弟在你监狱里遭遇的任何事
...anything that happens
to my brother in your prison,
我会让你也尝尝
I'll make sure happens to you.
明白吗？
Okay?
我也是个言而有信的人
I, too, am a man of my word.
谢了 你还好吗
Thank you. You okay?
对
Yeah.
我觉得
是时候重新指派卡尼了
I think
it's time to reassign Carney.
- 这么快？
- 嗯
- So soon?
- Yeah.
过去的痕迹
早该第一天就做
Vestiges of the past.
Should've done it day one.
[引擎轰鸣声]
[engine revving]
这小子不知道好歹
Little man doesn't know
where his bread is buttered.
[呻吟，抽气声]
[groaning, wincing]
[呻吟] 操
操 操 操 操
[groans] Fuck.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
[大声呻吟]
[groaning loudly]
[卡拉汉] 检查你的邮箱
[Callahan]
Check your mailbox.
前门 兄弟
Front door, brother.
♪ 缓慢诡异的音乐 ♪
♪ slow, eerie music ♪
（♪）
♪
[凯尔轻声呻吟]
[Kyle groaning softly]
[呻吟，喘息]
[groans, pants]
[喘息声]
[panting]
（♪）
♪
[Callahan]
你需要分心
You need distraction.
抽几口不会得癌症
Few puffs won't give you cancer.
[火车铃声]
[train bell clanging]
[远处警报声响起]
[siren wailing in distance]
嘿 告诉我 拉斐尔有线索
Hey, tell me
Raphael's got a line
关于那个对我兄弟动手的混蛋？
on that motherfucker
who put hands on my brother?
听说有个小喽啰想扬名立万
Some shitcake trying
to make his bones, is the word.
是 有帮派吗？
Yeah, any affiliation?
没什么来头
None to speak of.
就是个普通的小角色
Just a garden-variety
Ritz cracker,
从大盒子里拿出来的 你懂吗？
straight from the big box,
you feel me?
如果是批准的 你应该知道 对吧？
If it's sanctioned,
you'd know it, right?
那些雅利安人几个月前就可能动手了
It's been months since them
Aryans could've made that play.
- 那俄国人呢？ - 不
- And the Russians?
- Nah.
红色恐慌结束了 宝贝 接受胜利吧
The Red Scare's over, baby.
Take the win.
[叹气] 波哥大在街头对付你 拉斐尔内部感觉到了吗？
[sighs] Well, Bogotá comes
at you on the streets,
他们在炫耀实力
Raphael feel that inside?
- 对 - 和任何人一样贪婪
They flexing.
但他们也很聪明 知道何时坚持 何时退让
- Yeah.
- Greedy as anybody,
- 妈的 妈的 - 还会装模作样
but they smart, too. Know when
to stand, know when to sit.
当他们有所图时
- Shit. Shit.
- And to play it up
但这些小冲突不是战争 迈克
when they want something.
- 还不是 还不是 - 不
But these little skirmishes
ain't no war, Mike.
隐身模式 __SUBX_FMT_1__papi.__SUBX_FMT_2__
- Not yet. Not yet.
- Nah.
哥伦比亚人不会动你兄弟 好吗？
Stealth mode, papi.
他们肯定在轨道上对付过俄国人
Colombians ain't gonna bother
your brother none, all right?
隐身模式 放屁
They sure as shit bothered
the Russians on the tracks.
对 确实 确实
Stealth mode, my ass.
确实
Yeah. Sure enough, sure enough.
你的扑克脸太烂了 邦尼
Sure enough.
因为我有东西要分享
Your poker face is for shit,
Bunny.
[笑] 对
That's 'cause I got something
to share.
- [邦尼轻笑] - 你觉得呢？
[laughing]
Yeah.
不是卡特尔干的莫斯科
- [Bunny chuckles]
- You think?
♪ 缓慢不祥的音乐 ♪
Wasn't the cartel did Moscow.
♪ 缓慢阴沉的声音 ♪
♪ slow, ominous music ♪
弗兰克·摩西 底特律的老家伙
Was it you, Bunny?
老天 是 是 我认识他 是
Frank Moses.
Oldhead out of Detroit.
俄国人是他的礼物
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, yeah, I know him, yeah.
没有礼物这种事 邦尼
Russians was his gift to me.
他妈的我给了你很多
There ain't no such thing
as gifts, Bunny.
操你个够
Fucking give you plenty.
别他妈瞎搞了
你在干嘛？
Quit fucking around.
What are you doing?
我们联手
We joining forces.
有个从没蹲过牢的前辈罩着我
I get cover from an OG
who ain't never done time.
他拿他的钱 我赚得多得多
He gets his dough,
I make way more,
你在你山谷中 得到了平静
you get peace in your valley.
听起来像是升级
Sounds like escalation to me.
不 没有
Nah, no.
那人花了几十年分散资产
That man spent decades
diversifying his assets,
现在他准备拿钱走人
and now he finna cash out.
在圣克罗伊度过余生 [笑声]
Spend the rest of his days
in Saint Croix. [laughing]
是啊 谁不是呢？
Yeah, who isn't, huh?
人生苦短
Life is short, man.
我正干着呢
这叫有上进心
I'm doing it right now, man.
I'm enterprising.
你清楚外人带来的负担
Well, look, you knew the burden
that outsiders bring upon us.
我们不必一直倒垃圾了 老兄
We don't have to keep
taking out the trash, man.
我可不敢带着这破玩意儿出门
I wouldn't
venture out with this shit
如果我没看到机会
if I didn't see an opportunity.
嗯？我可不想打没准备的仗
Yeah?
And I ain't going in blind.
我看到危险 你知道我会处理
I see the hazard,
and you know I'll handle.
我担心的不是你
Well, it ain't you
I'm worried about.
♪ 缓慢诡异的音乐 ♪
♪ slow, eerie music ♪
多谢
I appreciate that.
摩西要见你
Moses wants an audience.
对
Yeah.
那家伙做得对
I mean, that man coming correct.
- 好的
- 我带着敬意
- Okay.
- Coming with respect.
见见他 我就这一个要求
Just meet with him,
that's all I ask.
行 我去见他
Yeah, I'll meet with him.
拉斐尔找上对我兄弟动手的人
Raphael meets the man
put hands on my brother.
那混蛋会听得一清二楚的 迈克
That motherfucker gonna hear
that shit loud and clear, Mike.
清楚明白
Loud and clear.
♪ 缓慢阴沉的声音 ♪
♪ slow, ominous music ♪
（♪）
♪
[克莱德]
17号 有访客
[Clyde]
17, got a visit.
[锁鸣响]
[lock buzzes]
把手给我
Give me your hands.
后退
Step back.
出去
Step out.
[牢房门隆隆地关上]
[cell door rumbles shut]
走吧
Let's go.
♪ 缓慢诡异的音乐 ♪
♪ slow, eerie music ♪
（♪）
♪
[凯尔畏缩]
[Kyle winces]
嘿 克莱德 这里交给我了
你回去吧
Hey, Clyde, I got it from here.
Why don't you get back
去做你那些该死的数独
填字游戏 随便
to your fucking Sudoku,
crosswords, whatever.
我带走他
I'll take him.
不用强迫我 Carnoscopy
Ain't got to twist my arm,
Carnoscopy.
- [蜂鸣器声]
- 斯蒂芬斯 后退 我来搞定他
- [buzzer sounding]
- Stephens, hang back, I got him.
天哪兄弟
我他妈真对不起
Jesus Christ, man,
I'm fucking sorry.
[呻吟声]
这不是你的错
[groans]
It's not your fault.
迈克在多方运作
我他妈——
Mike's working every angle,
I'm fucking--
我向你保证 不会再有下次
I promise you,
this won't happen again.
[叹气] 好吧 我知道 [畏缩]
[sighs] All right. I know.
[winces]
[蜂鸣器响起]
[buzzer sounds]
[喘息声，呻吟声]
哦靠
[gasps, groans]
Oh, fuck.
- 等等 嘿 嘿 嘿 嘿
- [呻吟声] 嘿
- Hold on. Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
- [groaning] Hey.
看着我 看着我 嘿
Look at me. Look at me. Hey.
- 用鼻子呼吸
- [呻吟声]
- Breathe through your nose.
- [groaning]
用鼻子呼吸
慢慢站起来
Breathe through your nose.
Stand up slowly.
- [呻吟声]
- 慢慢站起来
- [groans]
- Slowly stand.
站起来 你能行的
[呻吟声]
- Stand. You got this.
- [groaning]
- 呼吸 呼吸 就这样
- [呻吟声]
- Breathe, breathe. Like that.
- [groaning]
我看到的是麦克吗
Is this, uh...
is this Mike I'm seeing?
不 是特蕾西
No, it's Tracy.
- [凯尔] 操，不行。
- [蜂鸣声]
- [KYLE] Oh, fuck no.
- [buzzer sounds]
- 不 不 不
- 不 不 不 现在看着我--
- No, no, no.
- No, no, no. Now, look at me--
她看不见我... [吸气]
She can't see me... [inhales]
- 她不能看到我这样
- 凯尔
- She can't see me like this.
- Kyle.
我不想让她看到我这样
I don't want her
to see me like this.
凯尔 看 看 看
Kyle, look, look, look, look.
我不想让她看到我这样
I don't want her
to see me like this.
停下来 停下来 快他妈的停下来 行吗
Hey, stop. Stop.
Just fucking stop. Okay?
- [呻吟] 妈的
- 你不能丢下她
- [groans] Fuck.
- You can't leave her
像那样待在下面
只会让事情更糟
down there like that.
It'll make shit worse.
她只会开始想象你遭遇了什么
She'll just start imagining
what happened to you.
快点 快点 快点
Come on. Come on, come on. Come
on, come on, come on. Come on.
走吧 兄弟
Come on, brother.
[退缩，呻吟]
[wincing, groaning]
[门关]
[door closes]
——我给你争取点时间
——好
- I'll buy you some time.
- Okay.
[凯尔叹气]
[Kyle sighs]
凯尔 到底怎么回事
Kyle, what the fuck happened?
没看上去那么糟
It's not as bad as it looks.
我该去见见那家伙
Guess I should see
the other guy.
他们带你去医务室了？
Did they take you
to the infirmary?
不需要了 特蕾斯
我没事
I didn't need it, Trace.
I'm okay.
得等医生检查
你说了不算
Not until a doc sees it,
you're-you're not.
你的肋骨是挫伤还是骨折 还不清楚
We don't know if your ribs
are bruised or broken.
—如果骨折了...
—拜托 拜托 求你了
- If there's a fracture...
- Please. Please, please.
...你可能内出血了
...there's a chance
that you're bleeding internally.
嘿 嘿 我说了我没事
Hey, hey. I said I'm okay.
呼吸会痛吗？
Does it hurt to breathe?
我不能去医务室 你知道的
I can't go to the infirmary.
You know that.
也许我去找新狱长问问
Well, maybe I go see
the new warden and ask
她这到底开的是什么破店
what kind of shop
she's fucking running here.
我跟卡尼说了 迈克在处理 特蕾丝
I talked to Carney,
Mike's taking care of it, Trace.
是 干得真漂亮
Yeah.
Bang-up fucking job so far.
[叹气声]
[sighs]
♪ 缓慢忧郁的音乐 ♪
♪ slow, melancholy music ♪
听着
Look...
如果你受不了来这里看到我这个样子 我理解
if you can't handle coming here
嘿 没有什么是我不能——
and seeing me like this,
I get it.
你不用来这里 我是说
Hey, there is nothing I can't--
没有什么我应付不了
You don't have to come here,
is what I'm saying.
我不想跟你吵
There's nothing I can't handle.
那可真糟
I don't want
to go 12 rounds with you.
那可真糟 好吧
Tough shit.
这就是你娶的人 凯尔 改不了的
Tough shit. Okay.
[笑] 我投降 我投降
This is what you married, Kyle.
Can't turn it off.
对 你最好投降
[laughs]
I surrender. I surrender.
我不会让你一个人 死都不会
Goddamn right you surrender.
我看到过家人不来探望的后果
I'm not leaving you alone, okay?
Not a fucking chance.
里面的人就会崩溃
I see what happens
when family stops coming.
所以别叫我停下 你知道我不会
The ones inside break.
我不会
So don't ask me to stop,
because you know I won't.
[叹气声]
[sighs]
我爱你
I won't.
对不起
I'm sorry.
咱们的小家伙怎么样？
I love you.
—[呼气]
—嗯？
How's our little guy?
嘿 来吧 来吧
- [exhales]
- Huh?
[特蕾丝抽泣]
Hey, come on. Come on.
[凯尔轻笑]
[Tracy sniffles]
出发 女士们 出发 上冰
[Kyle chuckles]
冰鞋要系紧
Let's go, ladies, let's go.
On the ice.
不想看到有人磨破脚踝
Skates are tight.
出发！
Don't want to see any
ankle-burners out there.
[模糊的叫喊声]
Let's go!
迈克
[indistinct shouting]
[迈克] 你他妈在这儿干嘛？
Mike.
—你在做社区服务？
—咱们小子怎么样了？
[Mike]
Fuck you doing here?
- 你做社区服务了？
- 咱们那兄弟怎么样了？
- You got community service?
- How's our boy?
他被打得半死 但卡尼说他没事
Ah, he's beat to shit,
but Carney says he's all right.
卡尼他妈的在干嘛
What the fuck is Carney doing?
有那个打手的线索吗？
You got a line on the hitter?
正在处理中
It's being handled.
我们知道是谁打了邦尼吗
We know who hit Bunny?
我们收留的那个哥伦比亚小子
屁都不放一个
The Colombian kid we took in
is not saying shit.
那事儿有点邪乎 能不能别提
There's some weird fuckery
with that. Can you not raise
那该死的冰球？
the fucking puck?
注意言辞
Hey. Watch your language.
- 该死 我的错
- 操你妈的
- Friggin' puck. My bad.
- Fucking Jesus Christ.
我让他们不用进少管所 妈的 老天
I'm keeping 'em out of fucking
juvie, man. Jesus Christ.
- 你就是这么做的？
- [史蒂维] 箱子里那小子
- Is that what you're doing?
- [Stevie] Kid we got in the box,
比这些家伙大不了多少
老兄 那双眼睛沧桑得很 迈克
not much older than these guys,
man. Ancient eyes, Mikey.
对 她多大
Yeah, how old we talking?
大概20 最多
Like, 20. Maybe, at the most.
这孩子见过不少骇人的破事
Kid has seen
some haunting shit, man.
我进去后 他让我滚蛋
I'm in there,
he just tells me to fuck off.
好吧
我可能已经喜欢上那家伙了
Yeah, well,
I might like the guy already.
- 我们从他那挖出来的最多英语
- [伊恩] 我们可以起诉
- Most English we got out of him.
- [Ian] We could charge
这该死的小子 我们要是知道
要起诉谁就好了
this fucking kid if we knew
who the fuck we're charging.
- 嗯
- 但指纹比对结果出来了
- Mm.
- But the prints came back.
他们哪儿都没去
什么也没查到
They went nowhere.
We got nothing.
放他走
Well, cut him loose.
♪ 缓慢 悬念的音乐 ♪
♪ slow, suspenseful music ♪
[伊恩]
说清楚
[Ian]
To be clear,
甩掉那个该死的毒枭士兵
cut loose
a fucking cartel soldier
谁朝巴尼·华盛顿开的枪
who took a shot
at Bunny Washington,
然后就对金斯顿的警察下手了？
then turned
on Kingstown's finest?
- 准确说是我和伊恩
- 准确说是我们
- Uh, namely me and Ian--
- Namely us.
你说你什么都没 对吧？
Well, you said you have nothing.
Right?
他手无寸铁 放了他 看看他去哪儿
He's unarmed. Cut him loose,
see where he goes.
迈克 等他搭上下一班去波哥大的破车时？
Mikey, when he gets on
the next bus to fucking Bogotá?
那我们还等什么
Then what are we doing?
我们现在知道的
不比刚才多 对吧？
We don't know any more
than we know now, do we?
哥伦比亚人在墙两侧耍威风
Colombians are flexing
on both sides of the walls.
看看
谁说了算
Let's see
who's calling the shots.
- 对
- 搞清楚
- Yeah.
- Figure that out.
[流水声]
[water running]
♪ 悬疑紧张的配乐 ♪
♪ suspenseful, pulsing music ♪
（♪）
♪
[呻吟声]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[无线电杂音]
[garbled radio transmission]
♪ 安静紧张的音乐 ♪
♪ quiet, tense music ♪
[伊恩] 快点 你他妈的
[Ian]
Come on, you fucker.
给点好消息
Give me something good here.
♪ 缓慢神秘的背景音乐 ♪
♪ slow, mysterious music ♪
（♪）
♪
这小兔崽子完蛋了
This fucking kid's doomed.
住在废弃的破地方
Living in an abandoned shithole.
什么 注定失败？
你总以为还有时间
[Stevie]
What, doomed? You grow up
在豪宅里？嗯？
[电话嗡嗡声]
- in a mansion? Huh?
- [phone buzzing]
可不是嘛 嘿 上尉
No shit. Hey, Captain.
[Walter] 需要你回警局 Ferguson
[Walter] Need you back
at the station, Ferguson.
我们正忙着呢 队长
Yeah, we're right in the middle
of something here, Cap.
- 不是请求
- [Ian] 挺重要的
- Not a request.
- [Ian] It's kind of important.
斯蒂维和我在蹲点
基诺正在赶来
- Stevie and I are on a stakeout.
- Keno's on his way.
我现在就他妈给你倒计时
I'm counting you down
right fucking now.
该死 船长在骂人
Shit. Captain's cursing.
他这是在给谁作秀呢
He's trying to put
on a show for somebody.
[汽车引擎启动声]
对
- [car engine starts]
- Yeah.
[手机振动声]
[phone buzzing]
[Bunny]
搞定了 迈克
It's done, Mike.
那条消息发出去了？
That message went out?
全面广播
Broadcast large.
弟弟今晚能睡个好觉了
Baby bro gonna sleep good
tonight.
Thanks, Bunny.
[抽鼻子声]
[sniffles]
妈的
Shit.
- 我又怎么了
- 外面有位贵宾在等你
- What'd I do now?
- You got a VIP out in chairs.
我们这里没有 VIP
We don't have VIPs here.
他说
他叫弗兰克·摩西
He says
his name is Frank Moses.
- [丽贝卡倒咖啡]
- 他一个人？
- [Rebecca pouring coffee]
- He alone?
他是 光凭他的名字就...
He is, 'cause his name alone
分量和后果都够重
carries enough weight
and consequence.
知道 我知道他是谁 瑞贝卡
Yeah, yeah, I know who he is,
Rebecca,
我知道他会来 只是不知道什么时候
and I knew that he was gonna
come. Just didn't know when.
现在知道了 谢谢
Now we do. Thank you.
麦克 我们跟底特律有什么业务
Mike, what business do we have
with Detroit?
不知道 没有
We don't. None.
不关我的事 也不关你的事
Not my business, not yours.
就因为你给我的钱不够在汽车城混
'Cause you don't pay me enough
for Motor City.
什么 想要加薪？
可以给你加
What, you want a raise?
You can have a raise
快如你问 这就是你想要的吗
fast as you can ask.
Is that what you want?
这不是玩笑
那人杀气腾腾
This isn't a joke.
That man's murderous.
在这鬼地方 谁不是呢
Who isn't, in this fucking town?
让他进来 你再也不用见他
Send him in, you'll never have
to see him again.
- 好吗 我保证 - [叹气]
- Okay? I promise.
- [sighs]
怎么了 你刚加薪
What's the matter?
You just got a raise.
你无价之宝
You're priceless.
我说 无价之宝
Priceless, I say.
[开门 关门声]
[door opens, closes]
摩西先生
Mr. Moses?
多谢 小姐
Thank you very kindly, miss.
摩西先生
Mr. Moses.
麦克拉斯奇先生
Mr. McLusky.
咖啡 水 都是易燃品
Some coffee, water?
They're both flammable.
[轻笑]
[chuckles]
我很好
I'm good.
- [清嗓子] - 那么 我能帮你什么
- [clears throat]
- So, what can I do for you?
- 有内应吗 - 里面多的是
- Got someone inside?
- Got plenty inside.
里面 六尺之下 天堂之上
Inside, six feet under,
heaven above.
这不是我寻求的外联
That's not the kind of outreach
I seek.
我们只有这种
Well, that's the only kind
we got.
只要门牌上还挂着你的名字
Well, whatever keeps your name
on the door
支票就源源不断
and the checks coming in.
你天赋过人 难以忽视
It is impossible not to notice
that you have a real gift.
怎么说
Yeah, what's that?
管理你的小镇
Taking care of your town.
我照顾朋友
Well, I look after my friends.
确实 我观察德弗林很久了
Indeed. I've been watching
Deverin from afar, some time.
他能守住阵地 不错
Impressive how he's able
to hold his own.
- 邦尼势不可挡 - [笑]
- Bunny is a force of nature.
- [laughs]
确实如此 确实如此
He is that, he is that.
但真正的统治需要时间
But true dominance takes time.
我在朋友身上看到自己的野心
I see my own ambition
in our friend.
我看到他的未来
I see his future.
也看到你的
See yours, too.
哦 哇
Oh, wow.
你是什么先知吗
Are you some sort of prophet?
先知除了在本乡本族本家 没有不受尊敬的
"A prophet is not without
honor, except in his hometown,
那是马可福音 6:4
amongst his family,
and in his own household."
主日学学的忘得差不多了
That's Mark 6:4.
我不是金斯顿人 迈克
Yeah. I'm a little rusty
on my Sunday school.
所以 作为外人 也许我能预言一二
It means
I'm not from Kingstown, Mike,
混久了 破事都能一眼看穿
so, maybe, being an outsider,
I can prophesy some.
我干这行这么久
简写就能看懂
Hustle as long as I have,
shit comes in shorthand.
学会何时买进何时卖出 谁虚张声势谁真有实力
You learn when to buy, when to
sell, who postures, who proves.
而你呢 孩子
已经证明了自己
And you, son,
oh, you've proved yourself.
我不知道能为你做什么
I don't know
what I can do for you.
我没什么
能给你的
There's nothing
that I can offer
你还没有的
that you don't already have.
你们又要迎来新一批外人
You're about to have
a fresh plague of outsiders
降临你的小镇
descend on your town.
已经开始了
It's already started.
难道你不想只有我吗？
And wouldn't you rather
it just me?
♪ 缓慢诡异的音乐 ♪
♪ slow, eerie music ♪
我知道你和邦妮
之间的约定
I know the arrangement
that you and Bunny have.
你倒是挺大方
It seems a bit generous
on your part.
不是 我赚了钱 邦尼分担了些风险
It's not. I make a profit, Bunny
shaves off some of the risk.
这是合伙关系
It's a partnership.
如果能更好地教育那兄弟 那就全是好处
And if I can better educate
the brother, it's all upside.
所以你总是置身事外
So, you're always once removed?
两次 或者三次
[轻笑]
Or twice. Or thrice.
[chuckles]
所以当麻烦来了
So when the shit rains down,
你的搭档都湿透了 你却没事
your partners, they get wet,
you don't.
[笑]
我的合伙人赚了
[laughing]
My partners profit.
他们知道风险
And they know the risk.
抱歉
Sorry.
我觉得我提供不了你需要的援助
I don't think I can provide
the outreach that you need.
你这套谦卑把戏不适合你
This humble-pie act
don't suit you.
德弗林赢了 都是因为你
Deverin's won because of you,
你所维持的
制衡与平衡
the checks and balances
you maintain,
你对法律的掌控
your control of the law.
墙的两边都有我的朋友
I have friends
on both sides of the wall.
我希望你的朋友也能成为我的朋友 迈克
And I want your friends
to be mine, Mike.
开个价吧
So name your price.
好了 我谢谢你的邀请
Yeah, look,
I appreciate the offer,
我知道芭妮也是
但我的回报是安宁
and I know Bunny does, too,
but my payout is peace.
或至少是个念想
Or at least the promise of it,
you know?
不是为了赚钱
Uh, not for profit.
我收手之前
请求你的祝福
Then I ask your blessing
while I shut things down.
你可能看到一些垂死挣扎
但我向你保证
You may see some death spasms,
but I promise you this:
有任何纰漏 德弗林和我都会谨慎收尾
Any loose ends, Deverin and I
will tie off with restraint.
那是在轨道上的限制装置吗
Was that restraint
on the tracks?
[笑声]
[laughs]
我刚完成你开始的事 迈克
I just finished
what you started, Mike,
与桑特和诺斯科夫一起
with Sunter and Noskov.
你投出了扎实的八局
You pitched
a solid eight innings,
我在第九局上场 锁胜
I came in the ninth
and closed.
感觉我们已经是搭档了
Almost like
we're partners already.
感激不尽
Appreciate this.
后会有期
I'll be seeing you.
嘿
[door opens]
[门关]
[door closes]
[模糊说话声]
[indistinct chatter]
[敲门声]
[knocks]
[沃尔特]
关上门
[Walter]
Shut the door.
请坐
不 不 我站着就好
- Have a seat.
- No, no, I'm good. I'll stand.
你有什么发现？
What'd you got?
播放录像
Run the tape.
♪ 缓慢 悬念的音乐 ♪
♪ slow, suspenseful music ♪
（♪）
♪
好 然后呢
Okay, and?
[伊芙琳]
这是我跟你说过的
[Evelyn]
It's what I told you.
伊恩 这就是我之前警告的
Ian, it's what I warned.
最后那个？
That last one?
那是你送查理回锚湾
That's you returning Charlie
to Anchor Bay
你离开莫里西家11分钟后
11 minutes after you left
Morrissey's house.
没去过的地方 怎么离开
I can't leave a place
I've never been.
伊芙琳 别这样
好吧 你想跑就跑
Evelyn, I mean, come on.
All right? You can run
那盘磁带 反复播放
that tape over and over again
整天如此
因为你懂
all day every day,
because you know
我开车的样子
你可看不到
what you're not gonna see
is me behind the wheel,
因为我当时他妈的没在场
'cause I wasn't fucking there.
船长——天哪——
I mean-- the Captain--
Jesus Christ--
没有车牌 也没有身份证
There's no license plate,
there's no fucking ID,
你知道吗
你屁都没有 对吧
and you know
you don't have shit, right?
所以你在这钓个毛 快点
That's why you're here
fucking fishing. Come on.
出于对本部门的尊重
我——
Okay, look, out of respect
for this department--
这纯粹是胡说八道
你根本他妈的不尊重人
That is a crock of shit. You
don't have any fucking respect.
我来是出于礼貌 伊恩
对两位都是
I'm here as a courtesy, Ian,
to both of you.
明白吗 因为我要去大陪审团 然后我
Okay? 'Cause I am going
to the grand jury, and I am
提起诉讼
只是时间问题
going to press charges.
It is just a matter of time.
根本没有什么狗屁证据
There's no fucking evidence.
纯属主观臆断 伊芙琳
That's just subjective
horseshit, Evelyn.
看到什么想要的没
尼斯湖水怪 肥猫王
You see anything you want--
Loch Ness Monster, fat Elvis.
你看不到车牌
那是你的车
- You can't see a license plate.
- That is your car.
你知道多少辆他妈的道奇Charger
You know how many fucking
Dodge Chargers
在密歇根州注册了吗？查一下
are registered in the state
of Michigan? Look it up.
他妈的证据
不是那个
Fucking evidence.
That's not it.
伊恩 我也不想待在这
Ian, I don't want to be here
any more than you do,
但我不能不做我的工作
but I can't not do my job.
你知道该怎么做
You know what you need to do.
- 你的...
- 自己留着吧
- Your, uh...
- Keep it.
给你时间消化
It'll give you time to process.
考虑一下后果
Consider the implications.
我们马上回复你 律师
Oh, we'll get right back to you,
Counselor.
你尽管威胁
I mean, you can
keep your threats.
你什么都没有 也从没有过
You don't have shit,
you never had shit,
你还是屁都没有
you still don't have shit.
真带了就会带来
祝你愉快！
If you did, you'd bring it.
Have a nice day!
天哪
I mean, Jesus Christ,
你把我带进那个该死的陷阱？
you walked me
into that fucking buzzsaw?
你他妈的是警察还是看门的
Are you a cop
or a fucking doorman?
- 但你过分了 伊恩
- 过分？
- But you were out of line, Ian.
- Out of line?
你就给我看这个？
我操
That's what you got for me?
Holy fuck.
真是太他妈有帮助了 队长
Super fucking helpful, Captain.
（♪）
♪
[模糊说话声]
[indistinct chatter]
[无线电杂音]
[garbled radio transmission]
CI团队认为这是报复
The CI team sees this
as retaliation.
暴力史
终于找上他了
History of violence
finally caught up with him.
这当然是报复
他有暴力前科
Of course it's retaliation.
His history of violence
包括对凯尔·麦克卢斯基的袭击
includes the assault
on Kyle McLusky.
老大哥展示他的影响力
Big brother showing his reach.
-[轻声吹口哨]
-抱歉 妮娜
- [whistles softly]
- I'm sorry, Nina.
都怪我 我本该早就预料到的
This is on me. I should've been
way ahead of this.
不 是我的错
No, no, this is on me.
这是现在的首要任务
This is the one priority now.
麦克拉斯基在我的监狱里耍不了什么花招
McLusky pulls no fucking strings
in my prison.
明白 我会照办
Understood. I'll make it so.
- 知道你会来 我知道
- [叹气]
- Yes, I know you will, I know.
- [sighs]
我们应付过更糟的吧？
We've dealt with worse, right?
我们有过吗？我不知道
Have we? I don't know.
天哪 这地方
God, this place.
[无线电杂音]
[garbled radio transmission]
[模糊说话声]
[indistinct chatter]
[叹气声]
[sighs]
[Mike] 嘿
[Mike]
Hey.
看看是谁
你怎么样？来，拿到了吗？
How you doing? Here, got it?
- 嗯
- 你没事吧
- Yeah.
- You okay?
[抽泣声]
你知道我不是
[sniffles]
You know I'm not.
是啊 听着
我警告过你的 崔斯
Yeah, look,
I tried to warn you, Trace.
也没什么区别
Wouldn't have made a difference.
这个家总是处于警戒状态
Constant state of warning
in this family.
对
Yeah.
[特蕾西叹气]
[Tracy sighs]
这整个局面简直是糟透了
Well, it's a... all-around
fucked-up situation, you know?
但Kyle在尽量适应 对吧？
But Kyle's making the best
of it, right?
对 [叹气]
Right. [sighs]
- 你能吗？
- 这是
- Can you?
- This is
我尽量往好处想
me making the best of it.
这不是他的错
It's not his fault.
我知道不是他的错 迈克
这一切都不是
I know it's not his fault, Mike.
None of this is.
[叹气声]
[sighs]
凯尔在做对的事
他对此深信不疑
And Kyle's doing the right
thing, and he believes that.
他置身其中时
也需要你相信
And while he's in there,
he needs you to believe it, too.
我不知道 我觉得那是胡扯 [抽泣声]
I don't. I think it's bullshit.
[sniffles]
特蕾丝 那你能不能装一下
Trace, well, then,
can you just fake it?
[叹气]
我把Mitch带回家了
[sighs]
I bring Mitch home
每晚回到空荡的家 Mike
to an empty house, Mike,
every night.
每天早上醒来 身边没有凯尔
一想到这件事 我就精疲力竭
I wake up every morning
without Kyle,
等我真的睡着才醒 这种情况很少见
wake up when I've actually
slept, which is rare,
担心他身上发生的事
worried
that what happened to him
他妈的每天都在发生
is-is happening
every fucking day.
- 我已经尽力在装下去了
- 嗯
- I'm faking it the best I can.
- Yeah.
嘿 听着
Hey, look, um...
我很抱歉 真的
I'm sorry. I really am.
还好吗？
[小Mitch哭闹声]
- Okay?
- [Baby Mitch fussing]
我知道你是
而且我知道如果可以 你一定会弥补
I know you are, and I know
you'd fix it if you could.
- [宝贝米奇哭声]
- ♪ 缓慢而戏剧性的音乐 ♪
- [Baby Mitch crying]
- ♪ slow, dramatic music ♪
凯尔能挺过去的唯一办法
就是他看到
The only way Kyle gets
through this, and he sees
这件事的另一面
是如果你支持他
the other side of this thing
is if you got his back.
毫无疑问 毋庸置疑 他必须知道
Without a doubt, without
a question, he's got to know it.
- [小Mitch大声哭闹]
- [Mike] 好吧
- [Baby Mitch cries loudly]
- [Mike] All right.
- 得走了 麦克 他饿了
- 对对
- I got to go, Mike. He's hungry.
- Yeah, yeah.
好的 知道了
需要什么就告诉我
Yeah, yeah. Let me know
if you need anything.
谢了
Thanks.
[小Mitch哭泣声]
[Baby Mitch crying]
♪ 缓慢忧郁的音乐 ♪
♪ slow, melancholy music ♪
[模糊说话声]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ 缓慢 悬念的音乐 ♪
♪ slow, suspenseful music ♪
（♪）
♪
[说西班牙语]
[speaking Spanish]
嘿 嘿 混蛋！
Hey! Hey, motherfucker!
- 退后 混蛋！
- [咕哝声]
- Back the fuck up!
- [grunts]
- 你他妈干什么？
- 我什么都没干！[咕哝声]
- What the fuck you doing?
- I ain't doing shit! [grunts]
哦 是吗？
你好像想钻进洞里
Oh, yeah? Looks like you were
trying to go into the hole,
混蛋 滚出去
你这呆子 不然我砸烂你的头
motherfucker. Get the fuck out
of here, you pinhead, before
你的脑袋要插进自己屁股多深 托雷斯？
I crack your skull open.
- 你他妈脑子进水了？
- 一切正常 道格
How far does your head have
to be up your own ass, Torres?
三步
- Are you fucking braindead?
- It's under control, Doug.
你活着算走运
Three paces.
业余把戏
You're lucky to be alive.
[喇叭声]
Some bush-league shit.
[远处警报声响起]
[siren wailing in distance]
[伊芙琳]
__SUBX_FMT_1__好 卡拉 只要__SUBX_FMT_2__
[horn honks]
说清楚 不用他出一分钱
好吗？
[Evelyn]
Okay, Karla, just
如果日结工资
不够他的日薪
make it clear that nothing
comes out of his pocket, okay?
我就自己给他写张支票
随你便
If the per diem doesn't cover
his daily wage,
[叮咚声]
I'll just write him
a check myself. Whatever.
♪ 紧张激昂的音乐 ♪
[dings]
[警笛声]
♪ pulsing, dramatic music ♪
♪ 诡异缓慢的音乐 ♪
[siren wailing]
（♪）
♪
哦 妈的
♪ eerie, slow music ♪
（♪）
♪
你还好吗 大个子？
Oh. Shit.
我太壮了
这紧凑型车太挤了
You good, Big Man?
能打扰一下说句话吗 女士？
I'm too big
for this subcompact bullshit.
[敲门声]
[knocking]
你正好找着我 卡尼
什么事？
Trouble you for a word, ma'am?
今天真是漫长的一天
You just caught me, Carney.
What's up?
别让你家人等着
It's been a day.
好 我不会耽误你太久
Let's not keep
your loved ones waiting.
你有家人吗 典狱长？
Yeah, I won't keep you long.
是的 卡尼 什么事？
You got family, Warden?
我之前看到一件事
一直挥之不去
Uh, yes, Carney, what is it?
托雷斯在吃饭时
和一个囚犯扯上西班牙语破事
I saw something earlier.
Something I can't really shake.
哦？
Oh?
哪个囚犯？
Torres was tangled up
in some Spanish shit
罗伯托·克鲁斯 哥伦比亚杀手
with an inmate at chow.
我来这里这么久
他就只会带来坏消息
Which inmate?
我明白 继续说
Roberto Cruz. Colombian hitter.
典狱长 恕我直言
Nothing but bad news
as long as I've been here.
我不知道
你从哪个乡村俱乐部调来的
I hear you. Go on.
典狱长 恕我直言
Warden, excuse me
for saying this.
我-我不知道
你从哪个乡村俱乐部来的
I-I don't know
what country club you came from,
但你们必须知道
我们关押的罪犯
but you both need to know,
the convicts we keep here,
这些家伙都是杀人不眨眼的
these guys are fucking killers.
他们是人渣中的渣滓
They are the worst of the worst.
你得保持距离 说真的
You need to keep your distance.
Seriously.
Cruz呢？
And Cruz?
那个混蛋？
That asshole?
五十英尺长的杆子 恕我爆粗
A 50-fucking-foot pole,
pardon my French.
无妨 我不介意
Pardoned and no offense taken.
你的经历带来洞见 卡尼 很感谢
Your experiences bring insights,
Carney. It's appreciated.
继续说
Keep it coming.
我去和托雷斯谈谈
I will have a chat with Torres.
但你要知道
我们已准备好管教这些囚犯
But know that we are prepared
to handle our wards,
不惜一切手段
any means necessary.
晚安
Have a good night.
- （♪）紧张戏剧音乐
- [公文包咔嗒合上]
- ♪ tense, dramatic music
- [briefcase clicks shut]
[引擎轰鸣声]
[engine revving]
[电话铃声]
[line ringing]
[点击声]
[clicks]
合作出问题 我需要知道
This partnership goes sideways,
I need to know.
摩西放弃的话 我需要知道
Moses cuts bait, I need to know.
[嗤笑] 嘿 去你的"你好" 迈克
[scoffs] Well, fucking "hello"
to you, too, Mike.
听我说——
And-- listen to me--
如果要抛尸
if you're gonna drop a body,
能不能在城外动手
can you please do it out of town
别让我的日子更难熬
and not make my life
more difficult
比现在更糟吗 谢谢
than it already is? Thank you.
哦 看来你见过他了？
Oh, I take it
you met the man, then?
是的 我做了
Yeah, I did.
然后呢？
And?
日复一日 巴尼
And it's day by day, Bunny.
你把导师看作圣地
我只看到机枪巢
You know, you see a mentor,
I see a machine gun nest.
[笑声] 他是有逃走路子
就是这么回事
[laughing] He a way out is
what the fuck he is.
我不承担任何新风险
I don't take on no fresh risk
没拿到半分钱
才不干这种烂事
without no payday,
not for this shit.
不用蛮力也能反抗
Don't need muscle
to put up a fight against
也不是那些神经质的哥伦比亚人
them twitch-ass Colombians, neither.
不 麦克 这破事 这联盟？
No, this, Mike, this shit
right here, this alliance?
一切都是为了家人
我在为家人拼
It's all about family,
I'm doing for mine.
我明白了
Yeah, I hear you.
我明白
I understand.
就像你为你家人做的一样 迈克
Same as you do for yours, Mike.
我们都欠着
We both owe something.
小兔 我不是说
摩西是
Bunny, I'm not saying
that Moses is
这是错误的做法
the wrong way to go here,
但如果你在等待接管他的王国
but if you're waiting
to take over his kingdom,
我可不抱希望
I wouldn't hold my breath.
[嗤笑]
你比那更了解我
[scoffs]
You know me better than that.
老家伙别催它
可关乎我的血脉？
Oldhead don't push it forward,
and it comes to my blood?
我要夺下他妈的王国
I'm taking his fucking kingdom.
保护属于我们的
Protect what's ours.
那才是重要的
That's what matters.
这才是最重要的
It's all that matters.
♪ 紧张悬疑音乐 ♪
♪ tense, dramatic music ♪
- [重叠的说话声]
- [音乐播放中]
- [overlapping chatter]
- [music playing]
[嘈杂的七嘴八舌声]
[loud, overlapping chatter]
[音乐大声播放]
[music plays loudly]
- [重叠的交谈声]
-***
- [overlapping chatter]
[引擎轰鸣声]
[engine revving]
- 派个人在前面
- [Lamar] 明白
- Put somebody out front, too.
- [Lamar] I got you.
克里斯
Chris.
嘿 你好吗
Oh, hey, how you doing?
见到你真好 老兄
见到你真好 是啊
Good seeing you, man.
Good to see you. Yeah.
大家好吗
How y'all doing?
你妈现在在哪
Where your mom at now?
嘿 宝贝 你怎么样？
Hey, baby, how you doing?
嘿 见到你真好 见到你真好
Hey, good to see you,
good to see you.
[交谈声，笑声]
[chatter, laughter]
先生 你还好吗？
怎么了？
- How you doing, sir?
- What up?
- 嘿
- 你们怎么样
- Hey.
- How y'all doing?
[嘈杂的交谈声]
[overlapping chatter]
凯文在后面的房间
Kevin's in the back room.
好吧
All right.
[嘈杂人声中隐约播放音乐]
[music playing
indistinctly under chatter]
♪ 缓慢诡异的音乐 ♪
♪ slow, eerie music ♪
你他妈在这干啥，黑鬼？
The fuck you doing
up in here, nigga?
Bunny 对不起 我——
Bunny, I'm sorry. I'm--
打个电话会死啊？
What happened
to a fucking phone call?
[女人笑声]
[woman laughs]
我不是有意冒犯
I-I don't mean no disrespect.
我……我只是想说句话
I... I just needed a word,
只是面对面
just face-to-face.
- 我没事
- 不 你有事
- No, I'm good.
- No, you're not.
你在我姐生日会上
You're at my sister's birthday.
你表现得像在派对上
You gonna act like
you at a party,
而他妈的要喝酒
还要说话
and you're gonna fucking drink.
And speak.
好
Okay.
我刚才在想……
So, I was... I was thinking.
- 嗯
- 也许是时候了
- Uh-huh.
- Maybe it's time
我放下锚点继续前行
I move on from the Anchor.
有什么需要知道的事？
Something I need to know?
这位新典狱长
This new warden.
我也做不了什么
Ain't-ain't much I can do.
换岗
懂吧？
Changing of the guards,
you know?
只是在想也许外面
能做更多事
Just thinking maybe there's more
I could do outside,
更重要的事
bigger things.
看，这就是你的问题
See, that's your problem
right there.
你做不了决定。
我来
You don't do the thinking.
I think.
只要你按要求办事
这引擎就能运转平稳
As long as you do what's asked,
this motor gonna hum.
没有什么能永远持续
Now, nothing gonna last forever,
但眼下也只能这样
but it is what it is right now.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
你只要玩游戏就好 好吗？
All you got to do
is play the game, all right?
你对付新狱长像老的一样
You work the new warden
like you did the old.
你把她迷得神魂颠倒 兄弟 来吧 兄弟
You charm the fuck out of her,
man. Come on, man.
你再敢靠近我家人
And you come near
my family again,
我要在你屁股上
开一枪 小子
I'm gonna put a bullet
in your ass, nigga.
[笑声, 谈话声]
[laughter, chatter]
[惠特尼] 我他妈当然知道你不是
[Whitney]
I know damn well you ain't
在我的派对上谈生意
doing business in my party.
弹跳
Bounce.
给那位年轻人一点免费建议
Just giving a little free advice
to the young buck right there.
是的 是的 有道理
Yeah. Yeah, that reasons.
没人愿意花钱听你的建议
Don't see nobody paying
good money for your advice.
[嗤笑]
天啊 你要提那事？
[scoffs]
God, you gonna go there?
- 噢 我去过那
- 好了 妹妹
- Oh, I've been there.
- Come on, sis.
我知道些破事
我见过些破事
I know some shit.
I've-I've seen some shit.
[嗤笑] 哼嗯，有本事来我的人生里待一天试试
[scoffs] Mm-hmm. Spend even
one day in my life, I dare you.
你试试40岁
还带着两个孩子？
Try being 40
with two kids, okay?
- [笑]
- 你见过不少了
- [laughs]
- You've seen a lot.
给我滚出去！
[轻笑]
Get your ass out of here!
[chuckling]
生日快乐 惠特尼
Happy birthday, Whitney.
- [笑声] 生日快乐。
- [轻笑]
- [laughing] Happy birthday.
- [chuckling]
[灯光嗡鸣]
[lights buzzing]
[卡拉汉]
兄弟，补给包。
[Callahan]
Care package, brother.
疼就吃吧
想要的话 管用的话
Take it for the pain,
if you want, if it helps.
没人规定医务室不能来找我们
No rule says
infirmary can't come to us.
[凯尔轻声呻吟]
[Kyle grunting softly]
[喘息声]
[wheezes]
[呻吟声]
[groans]
[喘息声]
[panting]
[低吼声]
[grunts]
[Callahan]
有些人没教养
Some people aren't raised right.
从未被教导爱人如己
Never taught to love
thy neighbor as thyself.
只是想告诉你
Just want to tell you,
那个变态混蛋给你的欢迎礼？
sick fuck that gave you
that warm welcome?
见上帝了
Met his maker.
你手长啊，兄弟
You got reach, brother.
从没见过罪犯替警察杀人
Never knew a con kill for a cop.
那就是异常之母
That's the mother of anomalies.
想听那个故事
Want to hear that story.
等你准备好了，我洗耳恭听
When you're ready, I'm all ears.
[叹气声]
[sighs]
♪ 缓慢阴沉的声音 ♪
♪ slow, ominous music ♪
[摇滚乐响起]
[rock music playing]
你是辛迪？
You Cindy?
我刚开始担心被放鸽子了
I was starting to worry
I got stood up.
不
Nope.
谢谢 听着
能给我一杯纯威士忌吗？
Thanks. Uh, look,
could I get a whiskey, neat?
想一块去了
Great minds.
对
Yeah.
[清嗓子]
[clears throat]
卡尼搞什么？
Fuck's Carney?
他说他十分钟后到
He said he's gonna be here
in ten minutes...
30分钟前
30 minutes ago.
是啊 没错 如果要丢球的话...
Yeah, right. If a ball needs
to be dropped...
- 听着，我...
- 谢谢
- Listen, I...
- Thank you.
我真不能再等了
I can't really w-wait around.
是吗？
你还有什么事？
That right?
What else you got going on?
我得哄三个孩子睡觉
I got three kids
to put to bed, so,
你直接告诉我
你需要什么？
why don't you just tell me
what it is you need?
我猜不是卡尼那伙人
I'm assuming
it's not Carney contingent.
- 对 不 不是
- 嗯
- Yeah. No, it's not.
- Hmm.
是关于你兄弟的？
It's about your brother?
对 凯尔
他刚被处理完
Yeah, Kyle.
He was just processed.
他可不好惹？
And he's not to be fucked with?
- 他确实是
- 是啊
- And he was.
- Yeah.
（♪）
♪
听着 真的很抱歉
Look, I'm really sorry.
我在盯着他
I'm keeping an eye on him,
他在康复
and he is healing.
听着 我哥坐牢是有充分理由的
Look, uh, my brother is doing
time for a very good reason.
他不是罪犯
他是个顾家的人
He's not a criminal.
He's a family man,
他不适合在里面生活
and he's not suited
for life inside.
那么 现在轮到你登场了
So, here's where you come in.
里面需要有个友善的人接待他
I need a friendly face
for him, inside.
我需要你帮我盯着他
I need your eyes and ears
on him for me.
等他醒了 带他去院子里
When he wakes up, to the yard,
去淋浴间 直到熄灯
to the showers, till lights out.
[麦克清了清嗓子]
[Mike clears throat]
好吧
Yeah, okay.
我打电话时你得接
I'll also need you
to pick up when I call.
你就是我的生命线
You'd be my lifeline.
我...刚结束训练没几天
I'm... a few days
out of training.
- 那就好
- 我完全是个生手
- That's good.
- I could not be more green.
[叹气] 好吧 听着
[sighs]
All right, look,
只要没惹到谁
as long
as I'm not pissing anybody off,
只要你没触碰DOC的任何红线
我就会接你的电话
or crossing any DOC red lines,
I will pick up your phone calls.
我偶尔会对他点头示意 行吗
I'll give him a nod
from time to time. All right?
行政隔离区囚犯流动性很大
You know, there is a lot
of inmate turnover in Ad Seg.
里面这些人是因为惹了很多麻烦才进去的
Guys in there 'cause
they cause a lot of trouble,
别人逃避 只因想回避
others 'cause
they want to avoid it.
是啊 看起来是这样
Yeah, it seems so.
告诉我到底谁他妈跟凯尔在一起
I need to know who the fuck
is in there with Kyle.
我需要那份名单
I need that list.
以防有人对他不利？
In case someone means him harm?
该死的没错
Goddamn right.
（♪）
♪
[微波炉叮的一声]
[microwave beeping]
[电视上模糊的人声]
[indistinct voices on TV]
看看是谁
Hey.
老爸 来了
Pop, it's coming.
等一下
Just give me a second.
[电视嘈杂声]
[TV chatter continues]
[卡尼抽泣声]
[Carney sniffles]
[抽鼻子声]
[sniffles]
...反手然后听着...
...backhand,
and listen over the...
只看精彩片段 从不看比赛
Always the highlights,
never the game.
- 我从来搞不懂
- [笑]
- I never get that.
- [laughs]
注意力时长
Attention span.
你觉得呢？
What do you think?
They got a shot this year, Pop?
我要活下去直到我...
I'm gonna stay alive until I...
直到我看见斯坦利杯举起 [轻笑]
till I see the Stanley Cup
raised. [chuckles]
我可不想你活那么久
I don't want you
staying alive that long.
[笑声]
[laughs]
会用刀叉吗？
You can handle a fork and knife?
我像病人 机灵鬼？
I look like an invalid,
smart ass?
嗯 小心 烫
Yeah. Careful. It's hot.
听着 我出去一下
一会儿就回来 行吗？
Listen, I'm gonna run out
for a little bit, okay?
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
- 别死啊，老家伙。
- [轻笑]
- Don't die on me, you old fart.
- [chuckles]
[抽鼻子声，叹气]
[sniffles, sighs]
[电视声模糊]
[TV playing indistinctly]
[叹气声]
[sighs]
[两记枪声]
[two gunshots]
[电视继续播放，声音模糊]
[TV continues playing
indistinctly]
[风呼啸声]
[wind whistling]
[电视声模糊]
[TV playing indistinctly]
[火车汽笛声]
[train whistle blowing]
- [电视低声播放]
- [狗叫声]
- [TV plays quietly]
- [dogs barking]
[播音员]
安东尼又增加了一个领先优势
[announcer]
Anthony added another lead
并以4-2结束
and closes it out, 4-2.